TB JOSHUA CRUSADE IN DOMINICAN REPUBLIC!!! | Nov 2017
It was foretold that when Christ would come to save us
the blind would see,
the lame would walk,
the demon-possessed would be set free,
the afflicted would be liberated,
the poor would be blessed.
Jesus lives and still works wonders today.
Are you ready to make His Word the standard for your life?
If you are ready, Christ is willing.
Join T.B. Joshua in Dominican Republic.
Destinies will be restored,
finances will be released,
the broken-hearted will be comforted.
24 & 25 of November 2017, Felix Sanchez Olympic Stadium, Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic.
Entry is free.
The Dominican Republic Crusade with T.B. Joshua -
be there!